## Rahul KumarFeatured Resume

Territory Manager seeking assignments in Sales Management, Marketing, Business Development, Territory Management, Revenue Generation, Distribution Management, Channel Sales, Branding, Product Promotions, Market Research, Client Relationship Management

Current Designation: Territory Manager (Sales & Marketing)

Current Company: CNH Industrial (India) Pvt. Ltd. (New Holland Tractors)

**Current Location: Bhopal** 

Pref. Location: Uttar Pradesh - Other, Madhya Pradesh - Other, Rajasthan - Other

Functional Area: Sales / BD

Role: Area / Territory Manager

Industry: Industrial Products/Heavy Machinery

Marital Status: Married

Total Experience: 7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Notice Period: 1 Month

Highest Degree: MBA/PGDM [HR AND MARKETING MANAGEMENT]

Key Skills: Area/Territory Manager, Sales Management, Marketing, Business Development, Territory Management, Revenue Generation, Distribution Management, Channel Sales, Branding, Product Promotions, Market Research, Client Relationship Management, Profit Accountability

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

ID: 6bfd2cb613582c3374Last Active: 18-Sep-20Last Modified: 18-Sep-20

Jump to SectionWork Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

A Competent professional with 7 years of experience in Sales & Marketing, Business Development, Channel Relationship Management and Team Management. Currently Working With CNH Industrial (India) Pvt. Ltd. (New Holland Tractors). As a Territory Manager. A Dynamic Professional with 7 years of experience in Automobile Sales, Marketing, Finance, Retail, Fund Management and Business Development.

Deft in handling the entire Sales and marketing Operations encompassing finalization of field works, functions etc.

Accountable For achieving business goals and increasing sales growth.

Ability in cementing healthy relationship with the clients for generating business and leading workforce towards accomplishing business and corporate goals.

Outstanding relationship building, training & presentation skills.

Experienced in identifying new markets to penetrate sales opportunities and recommending strategic plans to increase business. (Organize various sales promotion activities )

**Work Experience** 

CNH Industrial (India) Pvt. Ltd. (New Holland Tractors) as Territory Manager (Sales & Marketing)

Dec 2018 to Till Date

To manage dealerships to achieve the business parameters like volumes, market share, collection, deliveries etc.

Ensuring distribution network by appointing dealers for appropriate market coverage

Ensure availability of trained manpower in adequate quantity at dealerships

Facilitate the dealers and his staff for implementation various systems like MIS etc.

Ensure availability of appropriate service infrastructure and drive implementation of service systems for improving customer satisfaction.

Execution of events like local level sales promotion campaigns, product launches etc.

Train the dealer salesmen on pre-sales and sales processes, new product features / modifications

Track the competitor activities, capture feedback on performance of competitor (and our) products.

Implementation of specific incentive schemes for dealers

Liaisoning with financial institutions / banks for exploring new avenues for retail financing of product.

Tafe Motors and Tractors Ltd. (Eicher Tracrors) as Junior Manager (Sales & Marketing)

Nov 2017 to Nov 2018

Greaves Cotton Ltd. as Assistant Manager (Sales & Marketing)
Apr 2016 to Nov 2017
^ Back to Top
Education
UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Agriculture) from Narendra Deva University of Agri. & Tech. Kumarganj, Faizabad (U.P) in 2012
PG: MBA/PGDM (HR AND MARKETING MANAGEMENT) from swami vivekanand subharti university meerut (u.p) in 2017
^ Back to Top
IT Skills
Skill Name Version Last Used Experience
MS word, MS excel, MS power point
Windows, Internet
^ Back to Top
Languages Known
Language Proficiency Read Write Speak
English Expert
Hindi Expert